Ben Myers

UCLA undergraduate pursuing B.S. in Mathematics with three years of customer service experience, one year of educational experience, and five years of computer programming experience. Involved in software development, management, and business growth.

+1 561-374-4627 benl.myers01@gmail.com benlmvers.com github.com/benlmyers

Technical Skills Language

Swift JavaScript Python C++ HTML + CSS C# Java Rust

Environment

SwiftUI + UIKit Unity + Blender React Swina Git + Github Vue React Native Node.js

Education

Alexander W. Dreyfoos School of the Arts University of California, Los Angeles H.S. Diploma, 2020 | 4.0 GPA | 5.037 HPA | 1510 SAT | 33 ACT B.S. Mathematics, 2024 | 3.483 Major GPA

Experience

Founder and CEO Jan 2021 - Present

Flowductive - Self-employed

www.flowductive.com

· Self-built a cross-platform productivity app in SwiftUI.

- Captured the interest of VCs, including Insight Partners and Newchip Ventures.
- · Spoke at Bruin Entrepreneurs' "Introduction to UCLA Entrepreneurship" event in Sep 2021.
- Participated in 10-week intensive UCLA startup accelerator program with a \$5,000 grant.

Jun 2022 - Present CTO

Poppin Technologies - Part-time

· Redesigning and rebuilding Poppin's mobile app using SwiftUI.

- · Improving web page with content via deep links.
- · Restructuring the company's Firestore data structure.

iOS Developer Nov 2020 - Present

Yatco - Part-time

www.vatco.com

- Improved web SEO for a vachting MLS with 600+ visitors/day in traffic.
- · Parsed 2000+ yacht builder data objects from sites into JSON using a custom Python script.
- · Developed a mobile iOS and Android app using Open API to fetch and request yacht data.

iOS Developer Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Edvora - Internship

www.edvora.com

· Fixed various UI bugs and ported iOS to iPadOS in SwiftUI. · Used Git, Atlassian and Bitbucket to manage and complete issues.

Code Sensei Jan 2020 - Apr 2021

Code Ninjas - Part-time

www.codeninjas.com

www.joinpoppin.com

- Taught kids ages 7-14 how to code in languages such as Swift, JavaScript, Lua, and Python.
- · Directed several themed summer camps.
- · Assisted with and hosted routine online code learning sessions over Zoom.

Customer Service Agent

Dec 2016 - Jun 2020

Publix - Part-time

www.publix.com

- · Worked as an item bagger, then a cashier, then a customer service agent, for one year each.
- · Recognized 7 times for outstanding customer service and continually achieved "Exceeding Expectations" and "Role Model" marks in biannual performance evaluations.
- Promoted twice for demonstrated leadership and proactiveness.